{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ez","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"patli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"dovi","osnova2":"enja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"umbir","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"iznena","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"svi","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tako","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
